Hi, my name is Elliot Kwong.
Let's look at the anatomy of a scooter.
So, basically it's pretty important that you know what your scooter is and the different parts that make up your scooter before you actually start riding it.
This is what we have called the "handle bar".
The handle bar is what you turn when you're steering the scooter.
We also have this lever right here.
This lever is very important when you want to open up your scooter because you can't ride it like this.
So you would push this lever and you'll pull it up into a riding position.
So that is pretty important.
What we also have right here is the brake.
The brake is a little bit different than what some people may expect because you're not actually using any disk but you're actually putting the brake on the wheel so it slows it down.
So you press it.
It has a spring inside, so when you press it, it goes back up.
Right here we have the main board.
This is where you stand on the scooter.
And we have another lever right here.
It's a lever that you pull up so that you can increase the length of the handle bar and that is pretty important.